[
    {
        "question_index": 1,
        "question_text": "What color is Jim’s car?",
        "correct_answer": "yellow",
        "other_options": [
            "new",
            "fast",
            "small"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 2,
        "question_text": "Mr. Davis is building a house. What is he building?",
        "correct_answer": "a place to live",
        "other_options": [
            "a place to put his car",
            "a place to work",
            "a place to keep his supplies"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 3,
        "question_text": "John has lots of new ideas. What has he been doing?",
        "correct_answer": "thinking",
        "other_options": [
            "shopping",
            "hunting",
            "skiing"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 4,
        "question_text": "What should you do when you hear a question?",
        "correct_answer": "Answer it if you can.",
        "other_options": [
            "Get it again.",
            "Repair it immediately.",
            "Pay it as soon as you can."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 5,
        "question_text": "Be sure to use the proper forms. Which forms should be used?",
        "correct_answer": "the correct ones",
        "other_options": [
            "the long ones",
            "the usual ones",
            "the revised ones"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 6,
        "question_text": "Why did Mrs. Lopez sit down?",
        "correct_answer": "She wanted to rest.",
        "other_options": [
            "She wanted to leave.",
            "She wanted to wash.",
            "She wanted to walk."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 7,
        "question_text": "Which of these produces the energy to light a lamp?",
        "correct_answer": "batteries",
        "other_options": [
            "darkness",
            "time",
            "vitamins"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 8,
        "question_text": "Lieutenant Norris left the papers in his office.",
        "correct_answer": "He left them where he works.",
        "other_options": [
            "He left them where he sleeps.",
            "He left them where he eats.",
            "He left them where he dresses."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 9,
        "question_text": "Mary is the cashier in our office.",
        "correct_answer": "She handles the money.",
        "other_options": [
            "She cleans the floor.",
            "She answers the telephone.",
            "She types all the letters."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 10,
        "question_text": "The accident was caused by a speeding car.",
        "correct_answer": "The car was going to fast.",
        "other_options": [
            "The road was very bad.",
            "The road was very wet.",
            "The car was going uphill."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 11,
        "question_text": "The students went out of the classroom.",
        "correct_answer": "They left the classroom.",
        "other_options": [
            "They were out of paper.",
            "They became excited.",
            "They looked out the window."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 12,
        "question_text": "Why did Jim buy that ball?",
        "correct_answer": "to use in the game today",
        "other_options": [
            "in the store on the corner",
            "the day before yesterday",
            "for $8.00 plus tax"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 13,
        "question_text": "Mr. Leslie’s job is to regulate the machines. What does Mr. Leslie do?",
        "correct_answer": "He controls the machines.",
        "other_options": [
            "He makes the machines.",
            "He oils the machines.",
            "He sells the machines."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 14,
        "question_text": "He knows the formula for it. What does he know?",
        "correct_answer": "what it is made up of",
        "other_options": [
            "how old it is",
            "where it is",
            "when it will happen"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 15,
        "question_text": "If a man says that perhaps he will come. What does he mean?",
        "correct_answer": "He may or may not come.",
        "other_options": [
            "He can't come.",
            "He doesn't want to come.",
            "He definitely will come."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 16,
        "question_text": "Which of these might be made of plastic?",
        "correct_answer": "a comb",
        "other_options": [
            "a salad",
            "a bar of soap",
            "a candle"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 17,
        "question_text": "Tom has fast reactions. What does he have?",
        "correct_answer": "quick responses",
        "other_options": [
            "two movements",
            "eyeglasses",
            "a good automobile"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 18,
        "question_text": "Carl’s studying chemistry at school. What’s he studying?",
        "correct_answer": "basic substances",
        "other_options": [
            "foreign languages",
            "political systems",
            "important dates"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 19,
        "question_text": "The doctor looked at David’s eye. What was he checking?",
        "correct_answer": "his vision",
        "other_options": [
            "his hearing",
            "his taste",
            "his feeling"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 20,
        "question_text": "The heart is an important organ. What does it do?",
        "correct_answer": "It pumps blood.",
        "other_options": [
            "It digests food.",
            "It cools the body.",
            "It protects the spine."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 21,
        "question_text": "Margaret asked John to keep an eye on the children. What did she ask him to do?",
        "correct_answer": "to watch the children",
        "other_options": [
            "to find the children",
            "to help the children",
            "to feed the children"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 22,
        "question_text": "I was asked to instruct the man.",
        "correct_answer": "I was asked to teach them.",
        "other_options": [
            "I was asked to test them.",
            "I was asked to command them.",
            "I was asked to watch them."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 23,
        "question_text": "The children will slide on the ice.",
        "correct_answer": "They will slip.",
        "other_options": [
            "They will sit.",
            "They will fight.",
            "They will talk."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 24,
        "question_text": "By this clock it is exactly eight-thirty.",
        "correct_answer": "The time is 8:30 sharp.",
        "other_options": [
            "It isn't 8:30 yet.",
            "It is past 8:30.",
            "This clock says 8 o'clock."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 25,
        "question_text": "The little boy lied.",
        "correct_answer": "He didn't tell the truth.",
        "other_options": [
            "He didn't hide the shoe.",
            "He cried.",
            "He got sick."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 26,
        "question_text": "The waiter said we can sit anyplace we wish.",
        "correct_answer": "We can sit at any table.",
        "other_options": [
            "We must sit at a special table.",
            "We can't have a table.",
            "We can't sit at a reserved table."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 27,
        "question_text": "She has not seen the doctor yet.",
        "correct_answer": "She is still waiting",
        "other_options": [
            "She has already seen him.",
            "She has a prescription",
            "She is already well."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 28,
        "question_text": "Ralph owes the bank a lot of money.\nRalph is in _____.",
        "correct_answer": "debt",
        "other_options": [
            "movies",
            "class",
            "transit"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 29,
        "question_text": "Susan came at the time we were leaving. When did Susan come?",
        "correct_answer": "just as we were leaving",
        "other_options": [
            "before we left",
            "just after we left",
            "some time after we left"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 30,
        "question_text": "Why are those black shoes comfortable?",
        "correct_answer": "because they fit well",
        "other_options": [
            "because they are new",
            "because they are cheap",
            "because they look nice"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 31,
        "question_text": "The student relies on his dictionary. What does he do?",
        "correct_answer": "depends on it",
        "other_options": [
            "talks about it",
            "writes on it",
            "doesn't use it"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 32,
        "question_text": "Did she get her mail today?",
        "correct_answer": "Yes, she has it now.",
        "other_options": [
            "Yes, she sent it.",
            "Yes, she wrote it.",
            "Yes, she didn't remember."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 33,
        "question_text": "The irritated man went on his way. How was the man feeling?",
        "correct_answer": "angry",
        "other_options": [
            "happy",
            "generous",
            "pleased"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 34,
        "question_text": "If oil is spilled, you should clean it up immediately. When should you clean it up?",
        "correct_answer": "at once",
        "other_options": [
            "after finishing the job",
            "whenever you can",
            "an hour later"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 35,
        "question_text": "They compressed the material. What happened to the material?",
        "correct_answer": "It became smaller.",
        "other_options": [
            "It became longer.",
            "It became hotter.",
            "It became stronger."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 36,
        "question_text": "We told the sergeant that we had already made up our beds. What had we done?",
        "correct_answer": "put the sheets and blankets on the bed",
        "other_options": [
            "washed the sheets and blankets",
            "built out own beds",
            "piled the sheets and blankets on the bed"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 37,
        "question_text": "Many traffic laws have been revised.",
        "correct_answer": "They were changed.",
        "other_options": [
            "They were transferred.",
            "They were protected.",
            "They were preserved."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 38,
        "question_text": "Mr. Walton plans to attend the concert.",
        "correct_answer": "He intends to go to the concert.",
        "other_options": [
            "He does not expect to go to the concert.",
            "He does not like concerts.",
            "He expects to plan a concert"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 39,
        "question_text": "The humidity is high today.",
        "correct_answer": "The air is damp.",
        "other_options": [
            "The wind is high.",
            "The clouds are high.",
            "The atmosphere is dry."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 40,
        "question_text": "All the pilots of the first squadron accomplished their bombing mission yesterday.",
        "correct_answer": "They completed their assignment.",
        "other_options": [
            "They checked their machines.",
            "They failed in their mission.",
            "They returned with their bombs."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 41,
        "question_text": "One of the important rights guaranteed by the Bill of Rights is the right to assemble\npeacefully.",
        "correct_answer": "To meet peacefully is an important right.",
        "other_options": [
            "People have no right to assemble peacefully.",
            "Peaceful assembly is rarely guaranteed.",
            "There are no real important rights."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 42,
        "question_text": "The man did his duty.",
        "correct_answer": "He did what he was supposed to do.",
        "other_options": [
            "He did not want to do anything.",
            "He did whatever he felt like doing.",
            "He did not know what to do."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 43,
        "question_text": "We landed at the airport in New York. It’s huge.",
        "correct_answer": "It's big.",
        "other_options": [
            "It's convenient.",
            "It's interesting.",
            "It's modern."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 44,
        "question_text": "The mechanic found the ruptured oil line.",
        "correct_answer": "It was leaking.",
        "other_options": [
            "It was bending.",
            "It was loosening.",
            "It was straining."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 45,
        "question_text": "You have to go over your lessons.",
        "correct_answer": "You must study some more.",
        "other_options": [
            "You must find you new lessons.",
            "You may stop studying.",
            "The class is over."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 46,
        "question_text": "The animal’s growth was surprising. What was surprising about the animal?",
        "correct_answer": "the way it got bigger",
        "other_options": [
            "the way it moved around",
            "the way it changed color",
            "the way it found food"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 47,
        "question_text": "John glanced at his wristwatch. What did he do?",
        "correct_answer": "He took a quick look at it.",
        "other_options": [
            "He shook the watch with his hand.",
            "He examined it carefully.",
            "He set the hands to the correct time."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 48,
        "question_text": "Sarah told me that I was stupid and lazy. Why was I angry at Sarah?",
        "correct_answer": "because of her remark",
        "other_options": [
            "because of her appearance",
            "because of her memory",
            "because of her influence"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 49,
        "question_text": "The school will eventually add another branch.",
        "correct_answer": "Sooner or later another branch will be added.",
        "other_options": [
            "Another branch has been added.",
            "The school is not interested in another branch.",
            "Another branch will never be added to the school."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 50,
        "question_text": "Yesterday it drizzled all day.",
        "correct_answer": "There was a light rain.",
        "other_options": [
            "Sleet fell during the storm.",
            "It snowed all day.",
            "Heavy rains fell all day."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 51,
        "question_text": "Herbert’s income is very low.",
        "correct_answer": "He doesn't make much money.",
        "other_options": [
            "He doesn't have much time.",
            "He doesn't make much progress.",
            "He doesn't have much education."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 52,
        "question_text": "When you have a homework assignment, you should never put off doing it.",
        "correct_answer": "You should do it without delay.",
        "other_options": [
            "You should remove it immediately.",
            "You should not cancel it.",
            "You should put it away."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 53,
        "question_text": "Mrs. Powell told her students that they had missed the point.",
        "correct_answer": "They didn't understand.",
        "other_options": [
            "They couldn't hear well.",
            "They knew what she said.",
            "They lost something."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 54,
        "question_text": "Don’t worry about the accident. It’s all water under the bridge.",
        "correct_answer": "The accident can be forgotten",
        "other_options": [
            "The accident happened under a bridge.",
            "The accident was your fault.",
            "Water caused the accident on the bridge."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 55,
        "question_text": "The programming instructions on this new VCR will leave most people completely\nbefuddled.\nThe programming is _____.",
        "correct_answer": "baffling",
        "other_options": [
            "manageable",
            "user-friendly",
            "obsolete"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 56,
        "question_text": "Beatrice found many unusual shells.\nShe was walking  _____.",
        "correct_answer": "on the beach",
        "other_options": [
            "on the highway",
            "in the forest",
            "in the desert"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 57,
        "question_text": "W: How are you today, Mr. McMahan?\nM: I’m very well. Thank you.\nWhat do you learn about the man?",
        "correct_answer": "He feels good.",
        "other_options": [
            "He is sick.",
            "He feels happy.",
            "He is rich."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 58,
        "question_text": "W: Do you know Jim Blake?\nM: Yes, he’s in my squadron.\nWhat do you know about Jim Blake?",
        "correct_answer": "He is a military man.",
        "other_options": [
            "He is a businessman.",
            "He is a teacher.",
            "He is a farmer."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 59,
        "question_text": "W: Where are you going to get it?\nM: I’ll have to go to the drugstore.\nWhat does the man probably have to buy?",
        "correct_answer": "medicine",
        "other_options": [
            "furniture",
            "potatoes",
            "a suit"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 60,
        "question_text": "W: What does your company do?\nM: We construct houses.\nWhat does his company do?",
        "correct_answer": "builds houses",
        "other_options": [
            "paints houses",
            "sells houses",
            "designs houses"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 61,
        "question_text": "W: How will you get your dog to take that medicine?\nM: I’m going to inject it.\nWhat’s the man going to do with the medicine?",
        "correct_answer": "He's going to give the dog a shot.",
        "other_options": [
            "He's going to throw it away.",
            "He's going to make the dog eat it.",
            "He's going to cover the dog with it."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 62,
        "question_text": "M: I hear you had a new kind of test this morning.\nW: Yes, the teacher gave us a composite test.\nWhat kind of test did the woman have?",
        "correct_answer": "a test made up of several parts",
        "other_options": [
            "a very long test",
            "a very difficult test",
            "a test on mathematics"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 63,
        "question_text": "W: Did the major get your message?\nM: Yes, but I had to clarify it.\nWhat did the man do to the message?",
        "correct_answer": "made it easier to understand",
        "other_options": [
            "repeated it over and over",
            "made sure the major could hear it",
            "wrote it down several times"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 64,
        "question_text": "W: Is that snake harmful?\nM: It certainly is, so don’t touch it.",
        "correct_answer": "if the snake would hurt her",
        "other_options": [
            "if the snake would help her",
            "if the snake was edible",
            "if the snake was alive"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 65,
        "question_text": "M: Why isn’t Raymond working today?\nW: He has a bad backache.\nWhat probably happened to Raymond?",
        "correct_answer": "He lifted a very heavy object.",
        "other_options": [
            "He ate some badly prepared food.",
            "He stayed outside in the rain.",
            "He drank too much at dinner."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 66,
        "question_text": "M: What did you think of the book?\nW: The ending was very abrupt.\nWhat did the woman think?",
        "correct_answer": "She thought the ending was sudden.",
        "other_options": [
            "She thought the ending was good.",
            "She thought the ending was obvious.",
            "She thought the ending was sad."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 67,
        "question_text": "Do you ever east in a restaurant?",
        "correct_answer": "No,I never eat in a restaurant.",
        "other_options": [
            "No,I eat in a  restaurant never.",
            "No,never I eat in a restaurant.",
            "No,in a restaurant I eat never."
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 68,
        "question_text": "I see the girl.   Jake _____ also.",
        "correct_answer": "sees her",
        "other_options": [
            "see it",
            "saw him",
            "seen me"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 69,
        "question_text": "Select the correct sentence.",
        "correct_answer": "Don't put your hand in the garbage disposal.",
        "other_options": [
            "In the garbage disposal don't put your hand.",
            "Disposal don't put your hand in the garbage.",
            "Don't your hand in the garbage disposal put."
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 70,
        "question_text": "She  bought a _____ of stockings.",
        "correct_answer": "pair",
        "other_options": [
            "two",
            "foot",
            "deck"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 71,
        "question_text": "Manufacturing is usually done _____.",
        "correct_answer": "in a factory",
        "other_options": [
            "on a farm",
            "in the forest",
            "in the home"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 72,
        "question_text": "Cotton is the (princeipal) product of this state.",
        "correct_answer": "main",
        "other_options": [
            "secondary",
            "unpopular",
            "cheap"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 73,
        "question_text": "Karen asked the clerk, \"How much is this item?\" She wanted to know _____.",
        "correct_answer": "the price",
        "other_options": [
            "the condition",
            "the way out",
            "the kind"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 74,
        "question_text": "Adam wasn't able to go with us.",
        "correct_answer": "He couldn't go.",
        "other_options": [
            "He didn't want to go.",
            "He wasn't ready to go.",
            "He wasn't supposed to go."
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 75,
        "question_text": "We should _____ the museum on the base.",
        "correct_answer": "visit",
        "other_options": [
            "visiting",
            "visited",
            "to visit"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 76,
        "question_text": "Ali his money _____ by a thief last night.",
        "correct_answer": "was stolen",
        "other_options": [
            "has stolen",
            "stole",
            "had stolen"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 77,
        "question_text": "_____ is prohibited within the school zone.",
        "correct_answer": "Speeding",
        "other_options": [
            "Sped",
            "To speeding",
            "Speeds"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 78,
        "question_text": "In English, a word may have several different meanings; for example, the word \"precipitation\".\nAny form of water or ice which falls on the earth is precipitation. Rain is a common example of\none form. Snow, sleet, and hail are examples of the frozen forms of precipitation.\nAccording to this paragraph, _____.",
        "correct_answer": "precipitation may fall in different forms",
        "other_options": [
            "rain and snow are the same form of precipitation",
            "rain falls in many different places",
            "precipitation has only one form"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 79,
        "question_text": "Anna told her husband to watch the children. She told him ______.",
        "correct_answer": "that he should watch the children",
        "other_options": [
            "that she would watch the children",
            "that she saw him watch the children",
            "that  they would both watch the children"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 80,
        "question_text": "Mr. Brown said the weather is normal for this time of year. The weather is _____.",
        "correct_answer": "as usual",
        "other_options": [
            "very fine",
            "dry",
            "stormy"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 81,
        "question_text": "Sleet and snow are weather hazards. The term \"hazards\" refers to _____.",
        "correct_answer": "dangers",
        "other_options": [
            "signs",
            "pressures",
            "advantages"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 82,
        "question_text": "The mechanic adjusted the brakes.",
        "correct_answer": "reset",
        "other_options": [
            "removed",
            "lubricated",
            "cleaned"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 83,
        "question_text": "The driver violated the _____.",
        "correct_answer": "safety rules",
        "other_options": [
            "steep curve",
            "car parts",
            "fuel line"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 84,
        "question_text": "We'll write him as soon as we _____ when we're going.",
        "correct_answer": "know",
        "other_options": [
            "will know",
            "should know",
            "knew"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 85,
        "question_text": "He may fail the course if he _____ study.",
        "correct_answer": "doesn't",
        "other_options": [
            "shouldn't",
            "didn't",
            "wouldn't"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 86,
        "question_text": "_____ perfect rice can be difficult for many",
        "correct_answer": "To make",
        "other_options": [
            "Made",
            "Makes",
            "Is making"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 87,
        "question_text": "_____,the meeting went well.",
        "correct_answer": "Overall",
        "other_options": [
            "Provided",
            "In case of",
            "In spite of"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 88,
        "question_text": "My head is bare.",
        "correct_answer": "not covered",
        "other_options": [
            "large",
            "small",
            "cold"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 89,
        "question_text": "The instructor was amazed at the students' progress.",
        "correct_answer": "surprised",
        "other_options": [
            "happy",
            "relieved",
            "suspicious"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 90,
        "question_text": "What do we call the degree of hotness or coldness measured on a scale?",
        "correct_answer": "temperature",
        "other_options": [
            "thermometer",
            "barometer",
            "energy"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 91,
        "question_text": "The general is  _____ now, but he can see you tomorrow at 0900",
        "correct_answer": "present",
        "other_options": [
            "unavailable",
            "free",
            "unoccupied"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 92,
        "question_text": "I told Henry to stick to it.  I told him to _____.",
        "correct_answer": "keep trying",
        "other_options": [
            "use more glue",
            "get another job",
            "put it on a plate"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 93,
        "question_text": "The things I bought added up to $17.50.",
        "correct_answer": "amounted to",
        "other_options": [
            "afforded to",
            "arrived to",
            "averaged from"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 94,
        "question_text": "I'm _____ in buying a new raincoat.",
        "correct_answer": "interested",
        "other_options": [
            "interesting",
            "being interesting",
            "been interested"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 95,
        "question_text": "According to their records, Mr. Henley _____ on five times by the end of the year.",
        "correct_answer": "will have been operated",
        "other_options": [
            "is going to operate",
            "can operate",
            "is being operated"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 96,
        "question_text": "When did you last hear _____ your mother-in-law?",
        "correct_answer": "from",
        "other_options": [
            "by",
            "concerning",
            "until"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 97,
        "question_text": "Mr. Wilson is a very dependable young man.  When he tells you that he will do something\nfor you, you can always _____ him to do it.",
        "correct_answer": "count on",
        "other_options": [
            "cross up",
            "depend in",
            "count to"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 98,
        "question_text": "In an era of increasing emphasis on the role of global military air power, it became necessary\nto increase the distances airplanes could travel.  The propeller-driven airplane with its slow\nand limited range became largely obsolete.  It was replaced by planes with supersonic speed\nmade possible through jet-propulsion.  Today with the fighters and bombers have achieved\nmuch success in increasing their range capabilities. According to this paragraph, greater\ndistances can be flown by bombers through the use of _____.",
        "correct_answer": "in-flight refueling",
        "other_options": [
            "jet propulsion",
            "supersonic speeds",
            "increasing air power"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 99,
        "question_text": "The company had to go through a lot of \"red tape\" to get its plans approved.",
        "correct_answer": "bureaucratic procedures",
        "other_options": [
            "angry protests by workers",
            "quick preliminary meetings",
            "unexpected cost increases"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 100,
        "question_text": "An internal combustion engine releases poisonous _____.",
        "correct_answer": "fumes",
        "other_options": [
            "vents",
            "catalysts",
            "vibrations"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    }
]